//Questions and Options array

const quizArray = [
    {
      id: "0",
      question: "What is affecting Buriganga river?",
      options: ["Deforestation", "Pollution", "Heavy rainfall", "Cyclone"],
      correct: "Pollution",
    },
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "Where does a cyclone begin?",
      options: ["Ocean", "Hills", "Forest", "River"],
      correct: "Ocean",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "When do cyclone usually occur in Bangladesh?",
      options: ["Early spring", "Summer", "Late rainy season", "Late winter"],
      correct: "Late rainy season",
    },
    {
        id: "3",
        question: "What are the three mighty rivers of Bangladesh?",
        options: ["Ganges, Jamuna, Meghna", "Padma, Meghna, Jamuna", "Padma, Nile, Jamuna", "Padma, Meghna, Sundarban"],
        correct: "Padma, Meghna, Jamuna",
    },
    {
        id: "4",
        question: "What is a negative impact of flash flood?",
        options: ["Losing homes", "No electricity", "Low access to healthcare", "All of the options"],
        correct: "All of the options",
      },
      {
        id: "5",
        question: "Why do landslides occur in Chattogram specificaly?",
        options: ["They have many hills", "There is a lot of land pollution", "It is very windy", "Because of river erosion"],
        correct: "They have many hills",
      },
      {
        id: "6",
        question: "What kind of trees are found in the Sundarbans?",
        options: ["Mangrove", "Mango", "Watermelon", "Guava"],
        correct: "Mangrove",
      },
      {
        id: "7",
        question: "What is the major cause for deforestation in the Sundarbans?",
        options: ["Cutting mango trees", "Timber and prawn farming", "Landslides", "Cyclones"],
        correct: "Timber and prawn farming",
      },
      {
        id: "8",
        question: "What is salinization?",
        options: ["The soil becoming less salty", "The soil on the hills getting loose", "The river getting polluted with salt", "Salt water getting into the soil"],
        correct: "Salt water getting into the soil",
      },
      {
        id: "9",
        question: "Why are some places hotter than others?",
        options: ["They lack trees", "They are near the ocean", "They have too many rivers", "They are near hills"],
        correct: "They lack trees",
      },
      

  ];